A Guide to the Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University Postal Card Collection, 1906-1995, undated
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University Postal Card Collection,1906-1995, undated
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2002-025
0.5 cu. ft. 1 box
Collection includes eighty postcards. Dated cards range from 1906 through 1995, but many cards are not dated. Cards depict various subjects including campus views, campus buildings, football, Corps of Cadets, and Blacksburg views. Some of the postcards are postmarked and addressed to recipients, while some are blank.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University Postal Card Collection acquired by Special Collections over many years.
Scope and Content
Collection includes eighty postcards. Dated cards range from 1906 through 1995, but many cards are not dated. Cards depict various subjects including campus views, campus buildings, football, Corps of Cadets, and Blacksburg views. Some of the postcards are postmarked and addressed to recipients, while some are blank.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically by decade.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Blacksburg (Va.); Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Montgomery County (Va.); University Archives; University History; Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Contents List
- Undated (Box 1)
- 1900s (Box 1)
- 1910s (Box 1)
- 1920s (Box 1)
- 1930s (Box 1)
- 1940s (Box 1)
- 1950s (Box 1)
- 1960s (Box 1)
- 1970s (Box 1)
- 1990s (Box 1)